原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     小酸奶  草草  苏葵
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     鱼鱼魚  纸袋P  Caroline  张小满
后期     吉吉
总监     小酸奶
深入黑暗  第一季 第五集
下行
戴瑞克
我今晚飞纽约  我们可以聚聚  说说话吗  我想念我们在一起的时光了
爱你  J
该死
Fuck!
不是吧
Seriously?
好吧
Okay.
戴瑞克  我今晚飞纽约  我们可以聚聚  说说话吗  J
太好了
Oh yeah.
日期  2月13日  出发时间  晚11:45  登机时间  晚11:20
第49楼
第42楼
你何不来玩玩呢
等等  可以留下门吗
Uh, wait, wait, can you hold that, please?
谢谢  抱歉  非常感谢
Thanks. Sorry. Thank you very much.
我没留心
I...wasn't paying attention.
好啊  P5
Oh, nice, P5,
我可是在地底下呢
I'm all the way down in the dungeon.
那真糟
That sucks.
嗯
Yeah.
期待长周末吗
Lookin' forward to the long weekend?
情人节加总统日
Valentine's Day and Presidents' Day?
多难得啊
How often do you get that?
简直是完美风暴  是吧
It's like the perfect storm, right?
你太客气了
You shouldn't have.
是啊  忍不住嘛
Oh, well, you know, couldn't help myself.
至少你带了酒来
At least you brought the bottle of wine.
是啊  为一位客户谈妥了生意
Oh yeah, closed the deal for a client.
客户挺有档次
Classy client.
还算有档次吧
Eh, fairly classy client.
看看这个
Check out this guy.
某人心理有问题啊
Somebody's got issues.
是啊
Yeah.
还挺有艺术天赋
With their artistic abilities.
怎么回事
What the heck was that?
我们是停下了吗
Did we just stop?
开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
我看看
Let me see.
我们可以按呼叫按钮
We can hit the call button.
喂
Hello?
"有人接听时会闪灯"
"Flashes when call answered."
没闪啊
It's not flashing.
喂
Hello!
-喂  -警报呢
- Hello? - What about the alarm?
你要按下警报吗
You wanna hit the alarm?
不就是干这个用的吗
I mean, that's what it's there for, isn't it?
好吧
Yeah, I...
好吧  那我按了
Okay, I'm just gonna hit it.
没反应
Nada.
那个不是应该嗡鸣的吗
That supposed to, like, buzz or something?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在是毫无反应
They're not doing anything.
喂
Hello?
喂  我们被困在了电梯里
Hello, we're stuck in the elevator.
天呐
Oh, God.
我不知道  似乎是...
I mean, I don't know, looks like something is, uh...
肯定是电力问题
Must be something electrical or something.
这怎么可能
How's that even possible?
灯还亮着  电视屏也是
The lights are still on and so's the TV screen.
嗯
Yeah.
我们应该挺接近
I think we're pretty close to the, uh...
好吧  不行的
Yup, that's not gonna work.
看来我是没有超人力量了
So much for my superhuman strength.
看  有摄像头
Oh look, there's a camera.
喂
Hello!
有人吗
我们在这里
We're in here!
喂
Hello!
《2001太空漫游》里的人工智能
哈尔9000应该是在那里
I mean, I would assume HAL 9000 is up there
能看到我们吧
seeing this, right?
你是什么运营商
Hey, what service do you have?
-什么  -你有信号吗
- What? - Do you have a signal?
没有信号
I got nothing.
但我的手机在电梯里总是不好使的
But mine rarely works in elevators, you know,
其实在任何大都会地区都没信号
or any major metropolitan area actually.
我完全没信号
I've got zero bars.
我们在地下四层呢
Well, we are four stories underground, so...
或许我们就安静等会儿
I mean, maybe we just wait a minute or two
肯定有人在解决呢
and I'm sure someone's working on it.
希望如此
God, I hope so.
这里有夜班保安的吧
I mean, isn't there security here at night?
我真的不想在这里困到周二早上
I'd rather not be stuck here till Tuesday morning.
拜托  我得走了
Come on, hello! Gotta go!
你没事吧
You okay?
有事  我还赶航班呢
No, I got a flight to catch.
天呐  太糟了
Oh man, I'm so sorry.
但你没有幽闭恐惧症
You're not, like, claustrophobic
什么的吧
or anything like that?
你呢
Are you claustrophobic?
反正不太喜欢被困在狭小空间里
I'm not not claustrophobic.
你在几楼工作
What floor do you work on?
49楼
Uh, 49th.
卡勒-斯坦维奇
Color and Stanwich.
你在卡勒做什么
What do you do at Color?
我是客户主管
I'm an account supervisor.
是公共关系...
It's a public relations--
我知道  卡勒挺大的吧
No, I know, it's-- Color's huge,
你们占了有三层楼  是吧
you guys have like three floors, right?
嗯  其实是五层楼
Yeah uh, five actually.
菲尼根-哈特曼
Finnegan Hartman.
我的公司
That's where I work.
一家会计事务所
It's an accounting firm.
不是非常性感...
It's not the sexiest...
不是...
Not the...
但我是新人
But I'm new there, so...
你懂的
you know.
这种事以前发生过吗
Has anything like this ever happened before?
-电梯故障  -有时候
- In the elevators? - I mean, it makes some
的确发出些怪声音
gnarly noises sometimes but...
但一般总能正常上上下下的
it usually always goes up and down.
好吧
Well...
Well.
该死
Shit.
好吧  这样肯定能更大声
Okay, this'll be louder for sure.
救命
Help!
我可以喊得更响  就是P不好发出来
No, I can do better, it's just hard to get the P out
因为你...
because then you're kinda--
这样声量不一样
you're not getting the same volume on it.
救命
Help!
你来试试吗
Oh, you're gonna try it?
救...
He--
救命
Help!
我们不可能是楼内
We can't possibly be the last people
仅剩的人吧
in the building, right?
等等
Oh, hang on.
看看...
What--uh.
好吧  等一下
Oh, okay, hang on a second.
你拿一下
Can you hold that?
好吧
Okay.
知道吗  我有点子了
You know what, I have an idea.
我肯定猜得到
Oh, bet I can guess what it is.
是啊
Yup.
我们也算够熟了
I think that we've known each other long enough.
天花板上总有出口的  对吧
There's always an exit in the ceiling, right?
是啊
Yup.
-准备好了吗  -嗯
- Ready? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
-准备好了吗  -嗯
- Ready? - Yup.
你要完全上来啊
Oh, you're going all the way.
-嗯  准备好了吗  -好
- Yup, ready? - Okay.
-等等  行吗  -没问题
- Wait, ready? - No, I got it, I got it.
-没问题  -抱歉
- You're good. - Sorry.
-行的  准备好了  -嗯
- Got it. Ready? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
Yup.
我就知道当初该去做男拉拉队员的
I knew I should have been a male cheerleader.
追逐梦想永远不晚
Well, it's never too late to chase your dreams.
有动静吗
Anything?
怎么会没有逃生口
How is there no escape hatch?
就是啊  如果真发生了紧急情况
Yeah, I mean, what are people supposed to do
让人怎么办啊
when there's an actual emergency, right?
这还不算紧急吗
Is this not an emergency?
好吧
Okay.
你没事吧
What, you okay?
-嗯  -你没事吧
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - You okay?
-可以把我放下吗  -好  抱歉
- Yeah, can you just put me down, please? - Yes, I'm sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-嗯  -让我看看
- Yeah, I just-- - Let me see.
真的没事
Honestly, it's fine, I just--
我的自尊受伤更重
I bruised my ego more than anything.
好吧
Okay.
天呐
Oh my God.
我的航班
My flight.
过去多久了
How long has it been?
15分钟
Fifteen minutes.
感觉好像一小时
Okay, it feels like an hour.
现在真过一小时了
Now it's been an hour.
嗯  我是赶不上了
Yeah, I'm never gonna make it.
真遗憾
I'm so sorry.
-我好想哭  -不  千万别哭
- I feel like crying. - Oh no. Please don't cry.
-为什么  -我没带纸巾
- Why? - I don't have any Kleenex.
抱歉  我就是想活跃下气氛
Sorry, I'm just trying to lighten a shitty situation.
这简直太扯淡了
It's fucking bullshit is what it fucking is.
-阿门  -混蛋
- Amen. - Fucking motherfucker.
破烂玩意
Fucking piece of shit.
你个死破烂玩意
You fucking dick-sucking piece of shit!
你们这群白痴混蛋
You fucking mouth-breathing assholes,
人都哪去了
where are they?
说得对
I agree.
对了  我叫詹妮弗
I'm Jennifer, by the way.
我不...
I don't--
怎么了
What?
按说我们早该
You would have thought that we would have already
交换过名字了
exchanged names by now.
但  盖门
But... Guymon.
叫我盖就行
Guy.
认识你很高兴  盖
Nice to meet you, Guy.
我也很高兴认识你  詹妮弗
It's really nice to meet you, Jennifer.
很遗憾是在这样的情况下
I'm sorry it isn't under different circumstances.
真的  如果是换了人类史上
Actually, literally any other possible circumstance
任何其他的情况都比这样好
in the history of humankind would have been better.
真的吗
Really?
我可开心了
I mean, I'm having such a great time.
你常来这里吗
You come here often?
盖  我不知道
You know, Guy, I don't know
我能不能允许你问我这个
if I can let you ask me that right now.
我不是...
No, I'm not--
我一般先从
I mean, it's usually backed up with, like,
"可以请你喝点东西吗"开始
"Hey, can I buy you a drink?"
而实际上  我的保温杯是空的
and honestly, my thermos is empty
而我要渴死了
and I'm dying of thirst, so.
那...
Well...
不用多说了
say no more.
-不了  -我没长虱子的
- Oh no, I'm-- - I don't have cooties.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean that.
我不会用喝你的水的
I'm not gonna take your water.
我坚持
I insist.
要不我就得开酒了
It's either this or I pop open the wine.
是旋盖的吗
Is it screw top?
不是
No.
但
But...
恰巧了  相信吗
It just so happens, believe it or not--hang on.
等等  你会笑的
You wait, you're gonna laugh.
看
Hup.
天呐
Oh my God.
是啊  难说呢  是吧
I mean, hey, you never know, right?
真的是啊
Yeah, truly.
我不知道这表明了我们的什么问题  但...
I mean, I don't know what it says about us, but...
表明我们是好童子军
Well, it says that we're good scouts.
时刻准备着
We're always prepared.
詹妮弗  请吧
Jennifer, please.
就喝一口
Just a sip.
给你了
Keep it.
随你喝
Have however much you want whenever you want it.
天呐  谢谢
Oh my God, thank you.
-不错吧  -太棒了
- Is it good? - So good.
如果你包里还有双份奶酪汉堡
Now if you had like a double cheeseburger in the bag.
我往常都在裤子里塞一个的
You know, I usually keep one stuffed down my pants
但  作为安慰奖
but... as a consolation prize,
给你点好时[吻]吧
why don't you have some Kisses?
抱歉  这太唐突了
Oh, I'm sorry, that's just very forward,
但我接受
but I do accept.
帮帮忙  别让我靠近那瓶酒
Just do me a favor and keep the wine away from me.
我是个自带开瓶器的姑娘
I mean, I am a girl who's packing her own corkscrew.
而且我们应该省着来
Plus I think we should definitely save our rations. I mean...
谁知道我们要困多久
who knows how long we're gonna be stuck in here.
我觉得最糟的情况
No, I would say worst case scenario--
最糟情况  到周二之前
Worst case scenario, we're stuck here
我们要被困80小时
80 hours until Tuesday.
相信我  我算了
Yeah, trust me I've done the math.
你考虑过做会计吗
Have you ever considered a career as an accountant?
因为菲尼根-哈特曼或许
'Cause Finnegan Hartman might be
-是正合适你的地方  -拜托  别逗我笑
- just the institution for you. - Please, don't make me laugh.
会让我想尿尿的
It's gonna make me wanna pee.
没事  我保证  我不介意的
It's okay, I promise, I don't mind.
不要
No.
太丢人了
So embarrassing.
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
看着我
Look at me.
这就是一件你完全不能自控
It's just something that you have to do
而且你非做不可的事
that's completely out of your control.
我们都困了几小时了
We've been here for four hours,
很快  我也得做了
so pretty soon it's gonna be something I have to do too.
天呐
Oh God.
你肯定是那种完全不介意
You know, I'm sure you're one of those people
裸奔的人
that are super comfortable walking around naked
什么的
or whatever, but...
但我是个很注重隐私的人
I'm an extremely private person.
好吧
Okay, I just...
天呐  我需要空间
Oh God, I need my space.
我完全理解  所以我才要跟你说
I completely understand and that is why I'm telling you,
在那边占据你的空间
take your space over there
标记你的领地吧
and go mark your territory.
哪里
Where? Where?
就在那个角落里撒  我在这边
Go over there in the corner, i'll go over here,
转过去
turn my back,
你拿我大衣撒好了
and you can just go on my coat.
什么
What?
这大衣挺旧了  我不在乎的  真的
What, it's an old coat, I don't care. Honestly.
我回头再洗干净  或烧了
I'll get it cleaned or incinerated.
我不会在你大衣上撒尿的
I'm not gonna pee on your coat.
好吧
Okay.
那...
Well then...
用你的空保温杯吧
why don't you go in your empty thermos?
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
捂上你的耳朵
Cover your ears.
你尿了吗
You going?
现在我尿不出了
Great, I can't now.
-什么  -现在我尿不出了
- What? - I can't now.
想想尼亚加拉大瀑布
Just think about Niagara Falls
或是别人撒尿
or someone else peeing.
什么都听不到
Can't hear anything.
完事了
Well, that just happened.
嗯
Yup.
是啊
Yup, it did.
好丢人
That was embarrassing.
不
No, no.
记住  我们是一个阵线的
Remember, we're all in this together.
这里所有人
Everyone in here.
这下妥了
Well, it's official.
我错过了航班
I've missed my flight.
还有下个情人节嘛
Well, there's always next Valentine's Day.
盖  我真的感激你的努力
You know, Guy, I really appreciate your efforts.
虽然你的笑话都很冷
Even though your jokes are really bad.
那你得怪我老爸
Well, you can blame my dad for that.
我就是想
I guess I'm just trying to...
避免我们都疯掉
keep us from going completely insane.
我觉得你已经来不及了
I think you're too late on that one.
这样就行了
That'll do it.
我不撒谎...
I'm not gonna lie...
我起初还不确定
I wasn't sure at first.
给
Here.
但你是个好
But... you are a very good
困在电梯里的伙伴
stuck-in-the-elevator buddy.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还有别的伙伴吗
Do you have any other buddies?
你结婚了吗
Like are you married?
男友  女友
Boyfriend? Girlfriend?
有人会来救我们吗
Anyone who'd come and save us?
没有  全都没有
No, actually, none of the above.
我跟我的工作有种
I am in a kind of all-encompassing
无所不包的扭曲关系
dysfunctional relationship with my job
这对我们不是好消息  因为都没人知道
which is not good news for us because nobody knows
我今晚加班了
that I even worked late tonight
或是我有任何理由还在楼里
or that I would still be here for any reason at all.
这么说
And saying that--
这么大声说出来
saying that out loud is...
真的好让人郁闷  好可悲
kind of very, very depressing and pathetic.
你呢
You?
一样
Same.
那...
Well...
你非要赶的那趟
what about this, like, super important flight
超重要的航班呢  肯定有...
that you had to catch? I mean, there must have been--
我有
What, that I had someone
在等着我的人吗
just waiting for me?
发现我不见了的人
Someone who would know I'd be missing?
没有
No.
其实是一时兴起
It's kind of a spur of the moment thing.
说来话长
It's complicated, it's a long story.
如果你想谈谈这个
Well, if you wanna talk about it,
或任何事的话
or anything at all for that matter,
我反正哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
没什么好谈的
There's really nothing to talk about.
挺蠢的
I mean, it's stupid.
我就是想去给一个人惊喜
I was just gonna go surprise someone.
一个
Someone who...
都不知道我要来的人
didn't even know I was coming.
或许都不希望我去
Probably didn't even want me to come.
我们真登对  是吧
Quite the pair we are, huh?
等等  我以为...
Wait, I thought...
你要打开你的酒
You're gonna open your bottle of wine?
我觉得是时候了
Well... I figured it's about that time.
你确定吗
You sure?
反正都开了
Well, it's already done now.
我恐怕本来也只会再转送出去
I was probably just gonna re-gift this anyway, so.
再说  我们不要再自怨自艾了
Besides, we're done feeling sorry for ourselves.
那好
All right.
女士优先
Ladies first.
不赖
It's not bad.
虽然不好  但也不赖
I mean, it's not good but it's not bad.
我说了  还算有档次的客户
Hm, like I said, fairly classy client.
我们在庆祝什么
So what are we celebrating?
没死如何
How about not being dead yet?
这我愿喝
I'll drink to that.
不许看
No peeking.
怎么回事
What is that?
有人吗
Hello?
喂
Hello!
希望不是坏现象
I hope that wasn't a bad thing.
几点了
What time is it?
你真想知道吗
You really wanna know?
不想  但说吧
No, but yes.
几点了
Just what time is it?
周六凌晨1点
It's 1:00 a.m. Saturday.
周末开始了
The weekend's begun.
我们派对吧
Let's party!
我们会出去的  别担心
Hey, we're gonna get out of here, don't worry.
我们没事的
We'll be fine.
我知道
I know.
-好吧  -好
- So. - So.
可以告诉你件事吗
Can I tell you something?
嗯
Yeah.
我有事没跟你说实话
I wasn't completely honest with you about something
我有点不安
and it's been bugging me
所以我想跟你说实话
so I really wanna be straight with you.
好
Okay.
我之前暗示说我之前没在楼里
When I implied earlier that I'd never seen you before
见过你
around the building,
这其实不完全准确
um, that wasn't completely true.
因为我们当时...现在的
Given the circumstances that we were in--
情况
that we are in--
我就是不想
I just didn't wanna say anything
让你对这种情况  或对我
that might have made you feel even more uncomfortable
感到
than, you know, you already were
更加不安
with the situation or with me.
当时  我觉得如果我说
At the time, I thought that if I told you
我记得在楼里见过你
that I did recognize you from the building,
我怕你以为我是个
I didn't want you to think I was some kind of, like,
跟踪狂什么的
stalker or something.
好吧  你是说你见过我
Okay, so when you say you've seen me...
嗯
Yeah?
到什么程度
To what extent do you mean?
我在走廊里见过你几次
I just--I've seen you a couple times in the halls
主要是在大堂
and just in the lobby mostly.
我不觉得你是跟踪狂  盖
I don't think you're a stalker, Guy.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧
Well, right.
但是  再坦诚一件事
However, to be even more honest...
我之前看到你时
when I've seen you,
还注意到了你
I've noticed you.
我记得我还想
I just remember thinking to myself,
"她看上去挺阳光的
"Hey, you know, she seems like a pretty upbeat person
或许她人挺不错"
and she--perhaps she's even really nice."
"而且
"And...
她很漂亮
she's very pretty.
我真想认识认识她"
She's definitely someone I'd like to know."
好吧
Well...
现在你认识了
now you do.
而且
And...
我可以
I can...
证实  你确实是个
confirm that you are indeed
很不错的人
a very nice person.
谢谢
Thank you.
而且你还很漂亮
And you're also very pretty.
好了  准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
没有
No.
好吧
Okay.
-准备好了吗  -嗯
- Ready? - Okay.
你来
You go.
-一起吧  -好
- Together. - Okay.
-一  -二
- One... - Two...
三
Three.
糟了
Oh shit.
老天  对不起
Oh man, I'm sorry.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
-不  我很喜欢  -画得真好
- No, I love that. - This is so good.
-你捕捉到了...  -谢谢
- You have captured-- - Thank you.
其他人没见过的我
A side of me that literally no one has ever seen.
你知道吗
You know what?
你要打电话了
Oh, you're just gonna make a phone call.
不是
No.
如果我们活着出去
If we survive this...
我要用这个当头像
I'm gonna make this my profile picture.
我太荣幸了
Wow, I'm honored.
能知道人们对你真正的想法很有趣
It's kind of amazing to see how people really see you.
是啊  你就告诉我了
Yeah, you're telling me.
拜托  这个一点也不准确
Come on, that is not accurate at all.
我现在太饿了  根本没法正常思考
I'm like barely functioning right now from how hungry I am.
我也是
Oh, me too.
我脑子想的全是
All I can think about is, like,
大份多汁的甘蓝沙拉
a big juicy kale salad.
甘蓝沙拉
A kale salad?
我现在想的是厚厚一叠薄煎饼
Like, I'm thinking about a fat stack of pancakes.
浸润在枫树糖浆里
Like, smothered in syrup and--
一盘纯肉披萨
Deep dish meat pizza.
-天哪  -塔可餐车里的墨西哥煎饼
- Oh God. - Taco truck burrito--
好了  别说了别说了  不说吃的
Okay, stop, stop, stop, stop. No more food.
拜托  没得吃已经很难熬了
Come on, this is already painful enough as it is.
那我们聊一些
Yeah, we'll talk about something
没那么让人向往的东西
that is definitely much less desirable.
你想聊什么
What do you wanna talk about?
随便你
Whatever you wanna talk about.
橄榄球
Um...football.
不
No!
棒球  汽车
Baseball? Cars?
性爱
Sex?
机器人
Robots?
行  那我们聊聊性爱
All right, let's talk about sex.
不
No.
-你提的  -我在开玩笑
- You called it. - I was joking.
好吧  你想聊聊性爱
All right, you wanna talk about sex?
那我们说点有趣的
Let's make it interesting.
看着镜头
Okay, now look into the camera.
不
No.
我想让你说出你最狂野的做爱地点
And I want you to tell me the dirtiest place that you've had sex in.
好吧
Um, okay.
我的天  你想让我先说吗
Oh my God, do you want me to go first?
好啊
Sure.
好吧  拿着  你来录我
All right. Here, record me.
好
Okay.
拿好了
Got it.
好的
Okay.
图书馆
The library.
什么
What?
那是在大学
It was college.
我的男友和我
I mean, so my boyfriend and I--
我那时的男友
my boyfriend at the time--
想了个有趣的主意  我们每人选一本
had a brilliant idea that we'd each go get--
你知道那种烂俗的浪漫小说吗
you know those cheesy romance novels?
知道
Yeah.
我们每人选一本  然后念出来
So we'd get one of those and read out, like,
念书里最淫荡的部分给对方听
the raunchiest section to each other.
然后  一开始是开玩笑
And... it started off as a joke,
但我不知道
but I don't know,
后来让我来了性致
it ended up turning me on.
我不  我猜以前我没读过这种小说  所以
I don't--I guess I never read trashy novels before, so.
即使是含有那种
Even ones that include lines like,
-"紫色脑袋的战士"和...  -没错
- "Purple-headed warrior" and... - Exactly!
比如"她急促地喘息着  胸部被汗水浸湿"
Like, "Her heaving, sweat-glistened breasts."
好吧  停
Okay, stop.
你太擅长这个了
You're way too good at this.
好吧
All right.
来  轮到你了
Go, your turn.
好吧  我不知道自己怎么才能超过你
Okay, I don't know how I'm gonna top,
你的大学男友
you know, your college boyfriend
给了你一场传统的杜威十进图书分类性爱
giving you the old Dewey Decimal System.
说嘛
Come on!
很不幸  我只能说我真的没有
Unfortunately, I hate to say that I really don't have a...
一个能和你媲美的故事
a story that is comparable to that.
-我不信  -是真的
- I don't believe you. - It's the truth.
我为什么要撒谎
Why would I lie about that?
我应该在这编一个
I should be standing here making up
最淫秽  最刺激的
the raunchiest, most fucking amazing--
行  那就这样
All right, so then do that.
编一个在你无话可说的生活中你能想到的
Make up the most bullshit sex tale that you can come up with
最胡扯的性爱故事
of your unstoried sex life.
好吧  你真的想让我说
Okay, you really want me to?
好吧  我说到哪了
Okay, well, where am I?
我正在做一个项目
So I'm working on a new project
然后有这么个姑娘
and, uh, there's this girl
她也在项目里
who's involved in the project
而且她美极了
and she's fucking gorgeous,
绝对是个十分
ten out of ten,
简直就是行走的亚马逊女神
Amazon goddess walking the face--
我很着迷她  所有人都是
I'm obsessed with her. Everybody--
她是公司最性感火辣的人
she's the hottest fucking person at work
我整天对着她流口水
and I'm like drooling over her.
然后
And, um--
但我什么也没做  直到公司聚会
but I don't do anything about it until this big work picnic.
她简直美炸了  我们开始喝酒
She just looks banging and we start drinking,
大家都在喝酒
everybody's drinking,
然后突然  她靠近了我
and suddenly, she approaches me
我们喝了点酒
and we have some drinks
然后我们回到我的车
and then we kinda sneak back to my car
我们又玩闹了一会
and we're partying some more.
然后我们开始开车
And we're driving now
然后她说  "你的挡杆"
and she's--she's like, "Your stick shift--"
不  等等  这太明显了
No, wait, that's so obvious.
等等  等等
Hang on a second, hang on a second.
她就说
She's like,
"为什么这东西叫手套箱"
"Why do they call them glove boxes?"
她就是这么说的
She talks like that.
然后我回答"我不知道  如果你有手套
And I go, "I don't know, if you had some gloves,
可以把手套放那吧"
we'd put 'em on in there, I guess."
然后她看着我说
And then she looks at me and she goes,
"但我没有手套"
"Well, I don't have any gloves."
然后她慢慢地脱下
And then she slowly slides off
极度性感诱惑的
the most incredibly sexy
一条内裤
pair of underwear...
然后
And, uh...
她就  把内裤放进了手套箱
She just like, she puts 'em in the glove box and--
这太蠢了  我感觉好奇怪
This is so stupid, I feel so weird
很不舒服  这不是
and uncomfortable, it's not--
等等  什么  你可不能现在停
Wait, what? You can not stop there.
我的天  你脸红了
Oh my God, you're blushing.
这不是唯一一件
Well, that's not the only thing
现在我不由自主的事
that is starting to do something involuntary right now.
好吧  感觉涉及到隐私了
Hm, all right. That's pretty personal.
这是你
Well, that's...
你想听的  对吧
what you wanted, right?
本着坦诚相见的原则
In the spirit of being intensely honest,
这是  我们现在是在玩真心话吧
that's--I mean, that's what we're doing now, right?
-没错  -好吧
- That is correct. - Okay.
怎么了
What?
没什么  你就是
Nothing, you're just, you know.
你刚才说的
What you're saying is is that...
你说你现在来了性致
you're telling me that you're aroused right now.
是的
Yes.
靠  我真是
Oh, fuck, I'm so--
我过分了  对不对
So, I crossed a line, right?
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
这  我  天哪  真抱歉
It's-- I-- oh my God, I'm so sorry.
我想的不是这个意思
Wasn't what I was thinking.
我只是  你对我很诚实
I just--you know, you were being honest
我就想...
and I was just thinking...
没关系
that's cool.
没关系吗
It's cool?
你知道
You know...
还有句实话
another true statement.
我现在很想吻你
I'd really like to kiss you.
这也许不是个好主意
That's probably not a good idea.
是吗
Right?
好吧
Okay.
停
Stop.
好吧
Okay.
天哪
Oh God.
操
Fuck.
你太棒了
You are amazing.
我觉得自己会爱上你
I could fall in love with you.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
嗯
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我得知道你的想法
I need to know what you're thinking
因为说真的
because, personally,
我自己现在有好多想法
I'm having... A lot of thoughts
还有情感  然后
and feelings and, uh...
我想先听听你的
I'd really like to hear yours first.
好吧
Okay.
我在想
I was thinking that
昨天本该是我修复一切的一天
yesterday was gonna be the day that I fixed everything.
我打算周末飞到纽约
I was gonna fly to New York for the weekend,
给我前未婚夫一个情人节惊喜
I was gonna surprise my ex-fiancé for Valentine's Day,
然后复合
and get back together.
你懂的  原谅忘记过去
You know, forgive and forget everything
破镜重圆
and...patch things up.
重修于好
Make everything okay.
那现在呢
And now?
我还是要这么做
Now I'm still gonna do that.
别误会我
I mean, don't get me wrong,
在这发生的一切
what happened here was--
很有趣  考虑到现在的情况
it was fun and considering the circumstances...
非常地美好
it was surprisingly nice.
但我爱他
But I love him.
而且他和我所拥有的
And what he and I have,
是真情实意
it's real.
而这个
And this...
这也是真情
This--this is real.
我是说
I mean...
我是真的  你知道吗
I'm real, you know?
这一切  是真的
This is... real.
我想说的是
What I'm trying to say
这一切都是偶然
is that this, this was casual.
拜托
You know? I mean, come on.
我们只认识了一天
We've only known each other for one day.
听着  盖  我只是想对你坦诚相告
Look, Guy, I'm just trying to be honest with you.
这很棒
Which is--it's great.
其实感觉很自由
It's actually freeing.
其实每一段
You know, it's actually what
稳定的关系都该这样
every committed relationship should be like.
完全的坦诚
Just complete transparency.
你和你前任也是这样吗
Is that what you had with your ex?
完全的坦诚
I mean, complete honesty?
没有
No.
其实这就是问题
That was exactly the problem.
那你为什么要跟他复合
So then why are you going back with him?
如果你们关系真的不好
I mean, if it was really that bad.
就像
Like...
刚才发生的事
with what just happened.
我们俩的事
With us.
我们有很多过去
We have history.
而这
And this is--
这只是某种幻想
this is some weird fantasy.
詹
Jen...
我们有感觉
we connected.
你知道
You know...
他配不上你
he doesn't deserve you.
他都不想让你去  不是吗
He didn't even want you there, right?
盖  首先
Whoa, whoa, Guy, first of all,
你不认识他  好吗
you don't know him, okay?
你都不认识我
And you don't even know me.
是啊
Yeah.
听着  我不想太无礼
Look, I'm not trying to be rude,
但我们之间没什么
but we're not a thing.
嗯
Yeah.
你说得对
You're right, and...
等我们出去  我要带你约会
when we get outta here, I'm gonna take you out--
等我们出去
When we get outta here, okay,
你回你的生活
you're gonna go back to your life
我回我的生活
and I'm gonna go back to mine.
装作这一切都没发生吗
And just act like none of this ever happened?
很显然发生了啊
Obviously it happened.
拜托  我们不能当作这没发生
Come on, I mean, we can't erase that.
这也没关系  没事
And that's fine, really, all right,
但这不能改变我现在的感觉
but it's not gonna change the way that I feel now
也不会改变我之后的感觉
and it's definitely not gonna change anything later.
听着
Look...
不如我们这样想
why don't we think about it like this?
你现在有个狂野疯狂的性爱故事可说
All right, now you have this crazy sex tale that you can share.
好吧  但是
Okay, but like...
你难道不觉得这一切是
Don't you believe that this somehow, like,
这一切是
that all this was some sort of like...
命运吗
fate?
真有趣  就仿佛
It's so funny, it's like...
我们被锁在这小小的铁盒子里
Like we're locked in this tiny little box
但我们仍好像隔着千万里
but we're still a million miles apart.
盖  拜托
Guy, come on.
不
No.
没关系
It's fine.
都没关系了
Doesn't even matter.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
因为我们对彼此坦诚
Because we're honest with each other.
这是最重要的  对吗
And that's the most important thing, right?
在所有稳定的关系里
In every committed relationship?
就好像
You know, it's just...
你身上有某种气质
there's just something about you
让我想要对你坦诚相告
that makes me want to be so honest with you.
我想告诉你一切
I want to tell you everything.
我想告诉你比如说
I want to tell you things like...
我不是楼里新来的
I'm not new to the building.
我不是会计
I'm not an accountant.
我的名字不叫盖
My name isn't Guy.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
而且
And...
我早就注意到你了
I certainly have noticed you,
詹妮弗·罗宾斯
Jennifer Robbins.
我没告诉你我的姓
I didn't tell you my last name.
我注意你也不是一两次
But not just a couple of times.
而是几十次
Try dozens of times.
几百次
Hundreds of times.
比如
Like...
其实是每一天
every single work day, in fact.
让我看看
Let me see. Hm.
早上九点到
Arriving at 9:00 A.M.
总是最后一个走
Always the last one to leave.
晚上七点  或者八点
7:00, sometimes 8:00.
这个
This.
比如今晚
You know, like tonight.
就在你进电梯之前
Right before you got into this elevator.
我怎么会知道这些呢
And how do I know all that?
因为
Because...
大楼保安能看到所有人
building security guard sees everyone.
注意并观察着所有人
Notices everyone, watches everyone,
知道他们的行踪
knows all their comings and goings
每一天
every fucking day,
但没有人看见我们
but nobody ever fucking sees us
因为我们是一群
because we're fucking, fucking, fucking, fucking,
隐形人
fucking, fucking invisible!
你是保安
You're a security guard?
前台
Front desk.
楼里最繁忙的职位
Busiest place in the building.
地球上最孤独的工作
Loneliest job on the planet.
但我知道我不是一个人
But I know I wasn't alone in here.
我知道我能看到另一个人眼里
I know I was looking into the eyes of another human being.
是不是
Right?
我知道我和你共同经历过
I know I was sharing an experience with you.
我就在那
I was there.
在你身体里
Inside of you.
我们抱着对方
We were holding each other.
不是吗
Right?
这不是我编的
I'm not making that up.
我了解你  詹妮弗
I know you, Jennifer.
比戴瑞克了解的多了
More than fucking Derek knows you.
但很显然这对你还不够
But that's not enough for you, clearly.
这对你来说还不够
This wasn't enough for you, right?
我为你计划了整个周末
Everything that I planned this weekend, for you!
为你  詹妮弗
For you, Jennifer.
为我们
For us.
发生的这一切
Everything that happened.
但是  但是
But... but...
如果你想走
if you wanna go,
你可以走
you can go.
我的天
Ugh... oh my God.
你有钥匙
You've had a key.
是我疯了吗
Am I insane?
你把我锁在了电梯里
You had me locked in an elevator?
没错  我糟糕透了  没错
Mm, yeah, I'm fucked up, yeah.
我是个混蛋  对吧
I'm a fuckin' asshole, right?
我的天  我们还做了爱
Oh my God, we fucking had sex.
你以为自己是谁
Who the fuck do you think you are?
我要叫警察来抓你
I'm gonna fucking call the cops on you.
你要去坐牢
You're gonna go to fucking jail.
你要为这事坐牢
You're going to fucking jail for this,
你听见了吗
do you hear me?
你要坐穿牢底
You're gonna rot in fucking jail!
那可不行
I can't have that.
不
No!
不  不要  不要
No, don't... don't...
停  停
Stop... stop...
不  操
No... fuck...
操  天哪
Fuck... no!
你弄断了
You broke it?
不不不
No, no, no.
我操
Fuck!
我操  你个臭傻逼
Fuck you, you fuckin' piece of shit!
我要杀了你
I'll fucking kill you!
欢迎回来
Oh, hi, welcome back.
我敢肯定
Safe to say,
你不喜欢我刚才活跃气氛的方法
you didn't like my little icebreaker.
为什么
Why?
拜托  詹
I mean, come on, Jen.
这难道不是认识姑娘
What better way to meet a girl
最好的方法吗
than to set up a situation
困在一个地方让她了解你
where she has time to get to know you?
没有分心事和发短信
Away from distractions and text messages,
去和别人联系
to connect with another human being.
而现在  看看我们
And now, here we are.
我不仅成功了
And not only have I achieved that,
还跟你展开了一段感情
we practically had an entire relationship.
我们认识了  聊了天
We... we met, we talked,
了解了对方  做了爱
we got to know each other, we fucked.
吵架  还分手了
We fought, we broke up.
都在一个周末  一个房间
All in a weekend, all in a room.
你逃不掉的
You're not gonna get away with this.
-会有人来的  -不不
- Someone's coming. - No, no, no-- no.
没人会来的  詹
No one's coming, Jen.
其他的保安呢
What about the other security guards?
-肯定有好几个  -既然你问了
- There has to be several. - Well, since you asked,
本来这周末有三个保安值班
there were three of us scheduled for this holiday weekend,
首先我告诉菲利普我替他代班
so first I told Phillip that I would take his shift,
然后我告诉艾迪一样的事
and then I told Eddie the same thing,
艾迪交了个新女友
and Eddie's got a hot new girlfriend,
自然他迫不及待答应了
so, naturally, he jumped at the chance,
所以詹  周二之前没人会来
so, no, Jen, no one is coming until Tuesday.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
你也跟我困在这了
You're stuck in here with me too.
是啊  没错
Yeah, that's right.
你让我们俩都陷入了困境  不是吗
You really fucked it up for both of us, didn't you?
所以我该想想该怎么办
So I've gotta figure out what to do with you.
因为我告诉你
Because I'll tell you right now,
我宁愿杀了你  也不愿回去坐牢
I'd rather kill you than go back to prison.
你个怪物
Fucking monster.
-你个怪物  -不
- You're a fucking monster. - No.
不  我不是
No, I'm not.
你看  我没逼迫你做任何事
See, I never forced you to do anything.
没逼你做你不想做的事
Anything you didn't want to do.
我只是营造了这个氛围
All I did was encourage the situation.
营造了这个氛围
Encourage the situation?
你他妈绑架了我
You fucking kidnapped me!
不  我没有绑架你
No! I did not kidnap you!
你之前喜欢我的
You liked me!
我们有感觉了  你个婊子
We connected, you bitch!
但之后你搞砸了
But then, you fucked it up!
我感觉好多了
I feel better.
感觉好多了
我们拆礼物吧
Let's open some gifts.
介意我猜猜这是什么吗
Mind if I take a stab at what this is?
我们看看  这是同意了吗
Let's see, was that a yes?
什么
What?
我觉得不是乐高
Well, I'm not going with Legos.
我不知道
I don't know.
我们看看
Let's see.
"给戴瑞克  爱你的J"
"To Derek, love, J."
简短温馨
Nice and simple.
拆开看看
Mm, let's see.
詹妮
Jenny!
你不该破费的
You shouldn't have.
是大号  大号
Is this a large-- it's a large!
不会吧
No fucking way.
我有个想法也许...
I got an inkling that maybe...
你知道吗
you know what?
让我试试
Let me see.
看上去怎么样
How's it look?
谁能知道
Who knew
我和戴瑞克的尺码一样呢
that me and Derek were the same build?
看来你现在知道了
Well... I guess you know now, right?
好了  轮到你了
All right, your turn.
快点
Come on, please.
把盒子给我打开
Open the fucking box.
好吧
All right.
那我就来帮你一下
I'm just gonna help you a little bit,
剩下的可得你自己来
you gotta do the rest yourself.
把礼物打开  詹
Open the fucking present, Jen,
打开
Open it!
今天可是爱的日子
It's the day of fuckin' love.
快点
Come on, go ahead.
里面有什么
What is inside?
细支雪茄
Stogies!
这是什么
What's this?
我一直都很想试试这种
I've always wanted to try one of these guys.
还有一个很棒的打火机
And a really cool lighter.
怎么样
How 'bout that?
别一副我会伤害你的样子
Stop acting like I would fucking hurt you!
男人和雪茄到底是怎么回事
What is it about cigars and guys?
我们就是这么爱雪茄  它们不是...
We just fuckin' love them, aren't they--
它们就像
they're just like,
它们好像就有一种魅力
there's like a fascination with them, you know?
它们如此充满生殖器幻想
They're just like so phallic.
就像...
It's like...
就像你在吸一根冒烟的大屌  对吧
It's like you're sucking on a big, smoking dick, right?
你有什么淫秽的性爱故事吗
You have any, um, raunchy sex stories?
和雪茄有关的  你肯定有吧
With cigars? I bet you do, right?
没有
No!
来放进你嘴里
Put it in your mouth.
你看上去好他妈难过
You look so fuckin' sad!
詹  真的很可惜
Jen, it's really a shame,
因为我觉得这些礼物这么笨
because I do think with all these nice gifts,
你本来可以挽回戴瑞克的
you would've gotten Derek back.
情人节快乐  詹
Happy fuckin' Valentine's Day, Jen.
我很抱歉  詹
I'm so sorry, Jen.
我有时生气的时候会失去控制
I lose it sometimes when I get mad
我吓到了你
and I scare you.
我不想再吓到你了
And I never wanna scare you again.
你还能再给我们一次机会吗
You think you can give us another chance?
你不用现在就着急下什么决定
You don't have to make any decisions right now,
好好考虑一下  好吗
just--just think about it, okay?
看看这两个人
Look at these two.
你为什么不来
他们手牵着手
They're holding hands
漫步在夕阳下
in the sunset.
穿着浴袍微笑着指着我
Just pointing and smiling in their bathing suits.
看上去好开心
Look so happy.
阳光天空度假村
Sunny Sky Resort.
真美
So beautiful.
我想带你去那里
I wanna take you there.
而现在我们在这里
Yet here we are,
头顶上闪着讨厌的荧光灯
under these obnoxious flickering fluorescents.
除了这家伙  这家伙罢工了
Except for this guy, this guy's not workin'.
喂
Hello?
我们得跟人说说
Have to tell someone about that.
我们应该
We should...
让人来修修
point this out to maintenance.
现在又正常了
Now they're working.
他们这下不得不换掉那些灯泡了
Now they're definitely gonna have to replace that light bulb.
除非他们想换掉整个...
Unless they wanna replace the whole...
没有螺母
There's no screws.
这边没有螺母
There's no screws on this side.
我给你说个笑话
I got a joke for you.
换灯泡需要多少名保安
How many security guards does it take to change a light bulb?
一个都不用  因为我们不是门卫
None, because we're not fuckin' janitors.
但是门卫
But janitors
肯定也得换这些灯泡
have to be able to change these lights.
电梯顶的这一边
There can't be a solid ceiling
不可能是封死的  对吧
on the other side of this panel, right?
如果我能打破这块板
If I could just break through this panel.
等等
Hang on.
来吧
Here we go.
太好了
Oh yes.
天啊
Oh my God!
詹
Jen!
上帝啊
Holy shit!
我们自由了
We're free.
为什么我之前没想到呢
Why the fuck didn't I think of that before?
好了
Okay.
你能顶我上去吗
Can you give me a boost?
我从上面爬出去
I'm gonna climb up through the shaft.
我到大厅里后
When I get to the lobby,
再下来从外面把门打开
I'll come back down and open the doors from the outside,
我会把你救出去的  好吗
I'll get you outta here, okay?
不  我觉得还是你顶我上去比较好
No, I think it's gonna be easier if you boost me.
-不不不  -你好好想想
- No, no, no. - Think about it,
我没有足够的力气把你顶上去  而且
I don't have enough strength to push you up, and...
我会完全照你说的做
and I'll do anything that you say,
你只要教我就行了
you just talk me through it.
什么  不行  那上面太高了  听着
What? No, that's a real climb. Look.
我知道该去哪里  你...
I know where everything is already, so just--
我会救我们出去的  好吗
I'm gonna get us out of here, okay?
我相信  但我就是担心等你出去了
I believe you but I'm just worried that when you get out,
你会改变主意
you're gonna change your mind,
你不会回来救我了
you're not gonna wanna come back for me.
你会把我扔在这里
You'll just leave me in here
然后你会报警什么的
and you'll call the cops Or something.
我们只能互相信任了  好吗
We're just gonna have to trust each other, okay?
我不会报警的
I'm not gonna call the cops.
谁会这么做
Who would even do that?
我们经历了这么多
After everything that we've been through?
-我就想离开这里  -我真的很想  我...
- I just wanna get out of here. - I really want to, and I...
我...
and I...
我不希望你进监狱
I don't want you to go to jail.
你说得对
You know, you're right.
这都是一场误会
It was all a misunderstanding.
我会救我们出去的  然后
I'll get us out of there, and then...
然后我们可以去那个度假村
and then we can go to the resort.
你知道吗
You know?
阳光天空度假村
Sunny Sky Resort?
拜托
Please.
把你的左脚放上来  好了
Put your left leg right here, here we go.
好了  完美
Okay, perfect.
跨一大步  上去
Big step, up!
你可以的  你可以的  你可以的
Come on, you got it, you got it, you got it!
太好了  完美
Yes, yes, perfect!
抓稳了  我要把你的脚放在...
Okay, hold on tight, I'm gonna put your foot...
抓稳了  准备好了吗
Okay. Hold on tight, ready?
把右脚放在我的肩膀上
Now, right foot on my shoulder.
完美  好了
Perfect, okay.
准备好了吗  准备好了就踩上去
Ready? And step up when you're ready.
太好了  很好  很好
Great. Good, good, good.
很好  继续  很好
Okay, keep going, nice.
完美  太好了  太好了
Perfect! Yes, yes, yes!
好了
Okay.
上面有一扇门  对吧
There's a door up there, right?
对
Yep.
好
Okay, good, okay.
你身后有一架梯子
There's a ladder behind you.
你应该能直接把那扇门推开
Should be able to just push that door right open.
那架梯子能爬上去  你看到了吗
Okay, that ladder goes all the way up, you see it?
去吧  爬上去
Go! Straight up.
我们成功了  我们成功了
We did it! We did it!
詹  不不不不不
Oh, Jen, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
不
No!
贱人
You bitch!
操  你这个贱人
Fuck, fuck you, you fucking bitch!
你这个贱人
You fucking bitch!
我要杀了你  詹
I will fucking get you, Jen!
我就应该杀了你
I should've killed you!
I could have killed you!
你
You.
太好了
Yes. Yes!
詹
Hey, Jen, hey!
你最好快跑
Oh, you better run...
因为  你要死了
'cause now, you're gonna die.
该死
Oh, shit!
你最好赶紧跑
You better fuckin' run!
救命
Help!
拜托
Come on.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
后退
Get back.
退回去
你踢断了我的鼻子
You broke my nose!
滚开  你这个疯女人
Get off, you crazy bitch!
操
Fuck!
你难道准备游出去吗
What are you, gonna fucking swim outta here?
你只会让我们弄得浑身是水或者被电死
All you're gonna do is get us soaked or electrocuted!
你听到我说话了吗  你明白吗
Are you listening to me? Do you get it?
没用的
It's not going to work!
这样应该能通知消防局了
That should cue the fire department.
混蛋
Fucking asshole.
不久就能出去了
It's not gonna be long now.
那现在呢
Well, what now?
你有什么计划
What's the plan?
不  詹
No, Jen.
不不不  等等
No. No, no, no, wait.
不  等等  等等  詹
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, Jen.
詹  看着我  不不不
Jen, look at me, no, no, no.
停下  停下  停下
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
不不不
No, no, no. No.
不
No!
我从来没听过一个成年男人这么求人
I've never heard a grown man beg like that before.
你有什么想对我说的吗
Did you have something to say to me?
-谢谢你  -谢什么
- Thank you. - For what?
谢你没有阉了我
Thank you for not disfiguring me.
你知道我们要怎么做吗
You know what we're gonna do?
我们要约法三章
You and I are gonna make a deal.
最后绝对不能变成
This is not gonna be one of those times when
我们获救后
they finally find us,
我报警
and then I call the cops,
我们俩各执一词
and it's your story against mine.
不可能
No.
我要确保你要为你对我做的事
I want guarantees, 'cause you're gonna go to
而进监狱
fucking jail for what you've done to me.
好吧  不要阉了我就行  求求你了
Okay, okay, please, just please don't do it, okay?
现在是2月115日  周日
It's Sunday, february 15th, and...
我还知道日期的唯一原因是
the only reason why I know this is because
我在我的手机上看到的
I saw it on my phone.
我跟一个自称是
I have been trapped in a elevator
大楼保安的人
with a man who claims to be
被困在电梯里了
the building security guard.
他说他的名字叫盖
He says his name is Guy.
其实不是  对吗
That's not right, is it?
是的
No.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
约翰
It's John.
你的全名
Your full name.
约翰·迪金斯
John Deakins.
这位迪金斯
So Deakins here,
他会告诉我们到底发生了什么
he's gonna tell us the truth about exactly what happened.
是我让我们被困在电梯里的
I caused us to get stuck in this elevator.
这不是意外吗
It wasn't an accident?
是的  是我故意造成的
No, I did it on purpose.
第49楼
太好了
Yes.
我趁你不注意时用我的钥匙关停了电梯
I used my key to stop the elevator when you weren't looking.
看看这个
Check out this guy.
计划不错
Nice plan.
我觉得有用吗
How did that work out for you?
我有自愿参与这一切吗
Now, was I a willing participant in any of this?
没有
No.
是你把我困在这里的吗
Did you trap me in here?
-我没有困住你  -说实话
- I didn't trap you. - Tell the truth!
是的  是的  是我困住了你
Ow! Yes, yes, yes, I trapped you.
你绑架了我  对吗
So you kidnapped me, right?
是的  我...我绑架了你
Yes.Yes, I kid... I kidnapped you.
-坐起来  -不行  我的背
- Sit up. - I can't. My fuckin' back.
-坐起来  -好吧  好吧
- Sit up. - Okay, okay, okay.
好吧  干什么
Okay, okay, what?
-你受伤了吗  -是的  是的
- You hurt? - Yes. Yes!
你伤害了我吗
And did you hurt me?
在我被困在这里的时候
When I was trapped in here?
是的
Yes.
怎么伤害的
How so?
我把你的头撞向地板
I hit your head on the ground...
我掐你
and I choked you.
然后呢
And?
然后我把你撞向墙
And I threw you against the wall.
所以你绑架了我
So you've kidnapped me.
并进行殴打
Assault and battery.
为什么
Why?
你为什么要这么做
Why do all of this?
因为我想见你  詹
Because I wanted to meet you, Jen.
那你为什么不像个普通人一样约我出去
So then why didn't you just ask me out like a normal human being?
因为你不会搭理我的
Because you wouldn't have given me the time of day.
你会拒绝我  我想
You woulda turned me down, and I wanted
你能好好和我进行对话
a guaranteed conversation with you,
我希望你能全神贯注
I wanted your undivided attention.
我觉得我值得你这么对我
I think I deserve that,
但其实呢  我只是一个保安
but no, I'm just a security guard,
但是你猜怎么着  我其实也不是保安
but guess what, no, I'm not, I'm not, actually.
那就是曾经的我
This was me.
那就是我曾经的人生
This was my fucking life.
约翰·迪金斯  菲尼根的执行副总裁
John Deakins, EVP at Finnegan's,
所以你才从来没听说过
that's why you've never heard of it,
因为根本不在这幢楼里
because it's not in this fucking building.
我曾经吹嘘公司里所有男的都想成为我
I used to brag the guys wanna be me at the company,
所以女的都想上我
the girls wanna bed me at the company.
你还记得吗  你还记得我和你说的那个性爱故事吗
You remember? You remember that sex story I told you
把内裤放进手套箱的那个
with the panties in the glove box?
那是真的  詹
That was true, Jen.
我的那个性感同事
That, that hot coworker of mine?
她想要我
She wanted me.
约翰·迪金斯
John Deakins.
人人都想巴结
Number one with a fuckin' bullet.
但其实故事不仅仅是那样  完整的故事是...
But it's not the whole story, the whole story is that...
也许是因为酒精
maybe it was the alcohol,
也许是因为她在车里突然发疯
maybe it was her being freaky in the car,
我完全没看到高速出口
but I missed that exit entirely
直接开出了车道
and I drove right clean off it,
冲进了峡谷
right into a ravine.
我的奥迪车翻滚了七圈
I flipped my Audi seven times.
要不是被那棵树挡住了  还会继续往下滚
It would've been more if it wasn't for that tree.
撞击撕裂了她的身体
The impact just obliterated her body.
当场死亡
Just killed her.
我的前额撞到了  我只受到
I had a bump on my forehead, that was
这点伤  然后
my only injury, and then later,
多亏了我请的超厉害律师
thanks to my fucking amazing lawyer
还因为我是约翰·迪金斯
and because I'm John fucking Deakins,
我只在监狱里蹲了六个月
I only got six months in jail.
但是等我出来以后
But when I got out,
由于我犯过罪
because I was a convicted felon,
我找不到工作
I couldn't buy myself a job.
我的积蓄终于用完了  于是
My savings finally ran out, and then,
我终于委身
I finally bent over
找了份保安的工作
and got this security gig,
原来的约翰·迪金斯可是根本看不上这种工作的
not something that John Deakins 1.0 would've ever done.
干了几个月后
After a few months of this shit,
我受不了了
it was fucking time.
我想再找回自己的感觉
I wanted to feel like me again,
我想成为他  好吗
I wanted to be him, right?
做回我自己
To be me again.
我曾经那么努力
I worked my whole fucking life for it.
我就想再找回那种感觉  一会儿也好
I just wanted to feel it, just for a little while.
为什么
Why?
为什么选我
Just why me?
因为是你不自觉中
Because you light up the entire building,
照亮了整幢大楼
you don't even know it.
你走进大堂
You walked into the lobby
穿着橘红色的大衣  我恨橘红色
in an orange jacket, I fuckin' hate orange,
这是世界上最难看的颜色
it's the worst fuckin' color in the world,
但是这也无所谓
but it didn't matter,
因为那根本比不上你带来的光亮
'cause it can't compete with you.
这就是原因
Anyways, that's why.
周一  2月16日  凌晨1点15分
等你看到这风景后就都值了
It's gonna be worth it when you see this view.
到了吗  我们快到了吗
Is this it? Are we almost there?
就快了
So close.
你最好别骗我
It better be.
你到底还来不来
Are you comin' or what?
拜托  宝贝  这里又潮又冷  我累坏了
Come on, baby, it's cold and wet and I'm exhausted!
我们不能直接回你家去吗
Can't we just go back to your place?
不不不  你肯定会喜欢的
No, no, no! You're gonna love this!
来吧
Come on.
这里真的没有人吗
There's really no one here?
我和你说了
Already told you,
只有一个我的同事
just one of the dudes I work with.
没什么好担心的
Nothing to worry about.
他人畜无害
He's harmless.
迪金斯
Yo, Deakins!
喂
Hey!
约翰
John?
小鲁  你干什么呢
Rube, what are you doing?
我以为你说你想上天台看看
I thought you said you wanted to see the roof!
不  我说我不想来了
No, I told you I was done.
这太蠢了
This is stupid.
等我一下
Hang here a sec.
别睡着了
Do not fall asleep.
迪金斯  你还在吗  伙计
Deakins, you decent, man?
出来  我带我女朋友来了  所以...
Heads up, I brought in my girlfriend, so...
约翰·D
我是约翰
Hey, this is John.
请在滴声后留言
Leave a message after the beep.
上帝啊
Holy shit.
喂  你们在电梯里听得到吗
Hello. Can you hear me in the elevator?
喂
Hello!
Hello?
你们听得到吗
Can you hear me?
有人吗
Is someone there?
你们听得到我说话吗
Can you guys hear me?
-喂  -喂
- Hello? - Hello!
你听得到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
我听得到  我能看到你  你们都没事吧
Yes, I can hear you, I can see you. Is everyone ok?
没事  救救我
Yes! Please help me!
你们没事吧
Are you guys all right?
救我出去  求你了
Get me out of here, please!
好吧  出了点故障
Okay, there's been a malfunction.
我这边看到电源关闭了
I can see that the power went out,
-以及...  -拜托快点
- and, uh - Please hurry.
快点  我们就在这里  拜托
Hurry up, we're in here, please!
我准备下去看看
I'm gonna come down there,
我要手动把你们救出来
I'm gonna let you out manually.
坚持住
Just hang tight.
拜托  快点  快点
Yes, please hurry, hurry!
小鲁
Hey, Rube?
有人被困在电梯里了
There's some people stuck in one of the elevators.
我要下去看看能不能把他们救出去
I'm gonna go down, see if I can get 'em out!
-你在里面吗  迪金斯  -我在里面  救命
- Are you in there, Deakins? -  I'm in here, please, yes!
我们被困了好几天了
We've been in here for days!
拜托  救我出去
Please, just get me outta here!
再坚持一下  好吗
Just, uh, hold on a sec, okay?
操  好吧
Fuck. Okay.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  等等
Okay, wait up!
把手缩回去  待在电梯里
Pull your hand back, okay? Stay inside the cab!
-小心点  不安全  -拜托
- Careful! It's not safe! - Please!
我先看看能不能把电梯降下来
Let me see if I can get this down the rest of the way first.
好的
Yes, okay.
喂
Hello?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
迪金斯  你在里面吗
Deakins, are you in there?
艾迪
Hi, Eddie.
到底怎么回事  伙计
What the hell happened, man?
你们被困在这里多久了
How long you been stuck in there?
给
Here.
用我的钥匙
Take my key.
插到控制孔里
Put it in the override.
没用
It's not working.
什么
What?
你能帮帮我吗
Can you help?
好吧
All right.
等等
Hang on.
我爬上来
I'm going to climb up and...
看看能不能启动
see if I can get this started.
等一下
Hang on.
卡住了
Stuck.
好吧
Okay.
搞什么
What the hell?
迪金斯
Deakins?
抱歉  艾迪
Sorry, Eddie.
等等  不
Wait. No.
什么  不  不  不
What? No. No! No, no!
不  不
No, no...
詹
Hey, Jen.
约翰·迪金斯
不好意思
I'm sorry, um,
你看到艾迪了吗
have you seen Eddie?
艾迪跑了[断了]
Eddie split.
晚安
Goodnight.
好吧
Right.
艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
你女朋友在找你呢
Your girlfriend was looking for you.
詹
Jen?
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
我知道过去几天发生了很多事
I know it's been quite a past few days
我希望告诉你
and I just want you to know,
我没想让事情发展成
I never meant for this to, um,
这样
go so far.
我真的很喜欢你
I really do like you.
我想
And I just think
也许在不同的境遇下
maybe in another life,
也许...
you know, maybe...
操
Fuck it.
詹
Jen!
操
Fuck!
什么
What?
不  不
No... no!
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no! No, no!